YWCA of the U.S.A. Records. Record Group 6. Program: Series V. Program Subjects
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES V. PROGRAM SUBJECTS
  - Subseries C. Music
    - Reference files, General
      - International Music Congress meeting, Sep 1968 (Box 634, Folder 15)
      - Japanese music, 1969 (Box 634, Folder 16)
      - Jazz, 1956-66, n.d. (Box 634, Folder 17)
      - Jewish music, 1950, 1959 (Box 634, Folder 18)
      - Labor union music, 1941-50, n.d. (Box 634, Folder 19)
      - Music therapy, 1925-44, n.d. (Box 634, Folder 20)
      - "Negro" spirituals, 1931-39, n.d. (Box 634, Folder 21)
      - Oratorio by Normand Lockwood "Brotherhood of Man," 1957 (Box 634, Folder 22)
      - Orchestras, 1940-60, n.d. (Box 634, Folder 23)
      - Recorded music
        - Use of recorded music in worship, Hobart Mitchell, consultant, 1955-70, n.d. (Box 635, Folder 1)
        - Use in program, 1956-69 (Box 635, Folder 2)
      - Resources
        - General lists, catalogues, 1948-65, n.d. (Box 635, Folder 3)
        - Library of Congress, 1935-60, n.d. (Box 635, Folder 4)
      - Rock and Roll, 1965 (Box 635, Folder 5)
      - Song Leading, 1933-56 (Box 635, Folder 6)
      - Songs, story behind, 1919-66, n.d. (Box 635, Folder 7)
      - Training, 1956-59, n.d. (Box 635, Folder 8)
      - United Nations songs, 1942-62 (Box 635, Folder 9)
      - World War II, 1941-44, n.d. (Box 635, Folder 10)
      - World Fellowship program materials, 1935-67, n.d. (Box 635, Folder 11)
      - Worship services
        - Ecumenical, 1945-65, n.d. (Box 635, Folder 12)
        - With themes, 1921-60 (Box 635, Folder 13)
      - Worship and the Arts
        - National Council of Churches publications, 1955-62, n.d. (Box 635, Folder 14)
        - Forum '68 On Media and Arts of Confrontation, Jun 1968 (Box 635, Folder 15)
    - Reference files, Sheet Music/Scores
      - Miscellaneous, 1941-64, n.d. (Box 635, Folder 16)
      - Civil Rights songs, 1960-64 (Box 635, Folder 17)
      - Folk Songs, n.d.
        - African (Box 635, Folder 18)
        - Austrian (Box 635, Folder 19)
        - Armenian (Box 635, Folder 20)
        - Belgian (Box 635, Folder 21)
        - British (Box 635, Folder 22)
        - Bohemian (Box 635, Folder 23)
        - Chinese (Box 635, Folder 24)
        - Cuban (Box 635, Folder 25)
        - Czecho-Slovakian (Box 635, Folder 26)
        - Danish (Box 636, Folder 1)
        - Dutch (Box 636, Folder 2)
        - Estonian (Box 636, Folder 3)
        - Finnish (Box 636, Folder 4)
        - French (Box 636, Folder 5)
        - German (Box 636, Folder 6)
        - Greek (Box 636, Folder 7)
        - Hawaiian (Box 636, Folder 8)
        - Hebrew (Box 636, Folder 9)
        - Hungarian (Box 636, Folder 10)
        - Indian (Box 636, Folder 11)
        - Indian, American (Box 636, Folder 12)
        - Italian (Box 636, Folder 13)
        - Jamaican (Box 636, Folder 14)
        - Japanese (Box 636, Folder 15)
        - Jugoslavian (Box 636, Folder 16)
        - Korean (Box 636, Folder 17)
        - Lithuanian (Box 636, Folder 18)
        - Moravian (Box 636, Folder 19)
        - New Zealand (Box 636, Folder 20)
        - Norwegian (Box 636, Folder 21)
        - Philippine (Box 636, Folder 22)
        - Polish (Box 636, Folder 23)
        - Russian (Box 636, Folder 24)
        - South American (Box 636, Folder 25)
        - Spanish (Box 636, Folder 26)
        - Swedish (Box 636, Folder 27)
        - Swiss (Box 636, Folder 28)
        - Syrian (Box 636, Folder 29)
        - Turkish (Box 636, Folder 30)
        - Ukrainian (Box 636, Folder 31)
        - Uruguay (Box 636, Folder 32)
        - USA (Box 636, Folder 33)
      - Girl Reserve song sheets, n.d. (Box 636, Folder 34)
      - Informal singing, National Recreation Association songbooks, n.d. (Box 636, Folder 35)
      - Labor Union songs, 1940-51, n.d. (Box 636, Folder 36)
      - National anthems 1917, 1941, n.d. (Box 636, Folder 37)
      - Parodies, 1946-50, n.d. (Box 636, Folder 38)
      - Peace, 1910-40, n.d. (Box 636, Folder 39)
      - Rounds and Canons, n.d. (Box 636, Folder 40)
      - Sacred music
        - Christmas carols, 1934, 1947, n.d. (Box 636, Folder 41)
        - Graces, n.d. (Box 636, Folder 42)
        - Hymns
          - General, 1947-58, n.d. (Box 636, Folder 43)
          - Ecumenical, 1950-62 (Box 637, Folder 1)
        - "Negro" spirituals, 1936-46, n.d. (Box 637, Folder 2)
        - Responses, 1932-55, n.d. (Box 637, Folder 3)
      - United Nations songs, 1942-55 (Box 637, Folder 4)
    - Training
      - General, 1951, 1963-64 (Box 637, Folder 5)
      - Creative Arts Workshop, Jun 1957 (Box 637, Folder 6)
      - Health Education Roundtable, Central Branch, YWCA of the City of New York, Oct 1958 (Box 637, Folder 7)
      - Initial Training "C," summer 1965 (Box 637, Folder 8)
      - Leadership Training Day, 1956 (Box 637, Folder 9)
      - Music Leaders Kit, circa 1944 (Box 637, Folder 10)
      - Music Workshops, Mar 8 & 9, 1947 (Box 637, Folder 11)
      - Music Workshop, Nov 1957 (Box 637, Folder 12)
      - Music Workshop Reference Material notebook contents, 1949-66 (Box 637, Folder 13)
      - National YWCA Institute on Program for Executive Directors and Program Directors, Nov-Dec, 1963 (Box 637, Folder 14)
      - Volunteer Training Institute, Ridgewood, NJ, 26 Nov 1952 (Box 637, Folder 15)
      - Workshop for Program Staff, Southern Region, Mar 1962 (Box 637, Folder 16)
      - Y-Teen Conference Leaders Institute, Eastern Region, Nov 1961 (Box 637, Folder 17)
      - Y-Teen Conference Leaders Institute, Nov 1962 (Box 637, Folder 18)
  - Subseries D. Pageantry and Drama
    - General
      - General and history, 1916-20 (Box 638, Folder 1)
      - Notes and resources, 1921-39, 1950 (Box 638, Folder 2)
      - Lists of plays and pageants
        - General, 1919-38 (Box 638, Folder 3)
        - Womans Press list, 1945-46 (Box 638, Folder 4)
      - Choral speech: clippings, resources, 1934-59, n.d. (Box 638, Folder 5)
      - General reference, 1961, n.d. (Box 638, Folder 6)
      - "The Use of Plays in Club Work," The Womans Press, 1930 (Box 638, Folder 7)
    - Scripts
      - "Above All Else, Liberty" by Georgia Tenger, TWP, 1929 (Box 638, Folder 8)
      - "An Adventure in Friendship" by Barbara Abel, TWP, 1923 (Box 638, Folder 9)
      - "The Adventures of Ella Cinders: An Idea for an Annual Meeting as Worked Out and Presented by the Columbus, Ohio, Association," program series #44, TWP, circa 1927 (Box 638, Folder 10)
      - "The Aftermath: A Playlet for the Week of Prayer," Oct 1914 (Box 638, Folder 11)
      - "The Air Route to Buenos Aires: A Program on South America" by Helen L. Willcox, TWP, 1929 (Box 638, Folder 12)
      - "Alice in Wonderland: A Dance Pantomime" by Mary E. Phipps and Marjorie Van Horn, TWP, 1927 (Box 638, Folder 13)
      - "Alice in Y Land" an original skit written by the Business Girls' Department of the Boston YWCA, TWP n.d. (Box 638, Folder 14)
      - "Amos," TWP 1926 (Box 638, Folder 15)
      - "And Who Can This Spirit Be?" by Emma Mauritz Larson, TWP 1920 (Box 638, Folder 16)
      - "At the Sign of the Boar's Head" by Vida R. Sutton, TWP 1924 (Box 638, Folder 17)
      - "At the Turn of Tide" by Georgia Stenger, TWP, 1921 (Box 638, Folder 18)
      - "At the YW: A Play of World Fellowship" by Maxine Wood, TWP, 1948 (Box 638, Folder 19)
      - "Ballad of the YWCA" for choric speaking, 1943 (Box 638, Folder 20)
      - "Beau and Belle: A Lyrical Trifle" by Constance Smedley Armfield, TWP, 1922 (Box 638, Folder 21)
      - "The Beloved Community and The Quest of the Understanding Heart" by Hazel Hardacre and Helen Hoskins, TWP Program Series no. 31, 1926 (Box 638, Folder 22)
      - "Bible Plays Out of the East" by Anna R. Kennedy, TWP 1929 (Box 638, Folder 23)
      - "Blood Doesn't Tell: A Play About Blood Plasma and Blood Donors" by Elsie Austin, TWP, 1945 (Box 638, Folder 24)
      - "The Bonds of Liberty: A Masque" by Josephine Thorp, TWP, 1919 (Box 639, Folder 1)
      - "The Bow of Promise: A Peace Festival" by Josephine Thorp, TWP, 1919 (Box 639, Folder 2)
      - "Bread and Butter Plus: A Vocational Guidance Play" by Hazel M. Lewis, 1938 (Box 639, Folder 3)
      - "The Brown Bull of Norway" by Margaret Lynch Conger, TWP, 1924 (Box 639, Folder 4)
      - "Bubbles: a World Fellowship Play of India and America" by Leah Adkisson Kazmark, TWP, 1931 (Box 639, Folder 5)
      - "The Budget Ghost" by Mary L. Carr, reprinted from The Womans Press, Oct 1923 (Box 639, Folder 6)
      - "Builders of Dreams" by Polly Cady, n.d. (Box 639, Folder 7)
      - "The Burning Altar: A Thanksgiving Ceremony" by Ethel Gesner Rockwell, TWP, 1930 (Box 639, Folder 8)
      - "Calling All Nations: A Pageant of Peace," TWP 1936 (Box 639, Folder 9)
      - "A Camel Trip to Cairo: A Program on Egypt" by Helen L. Willcox, The Womans Press, 1920 (Box 639, Folder 10)
      - "Canton Pearls: A Play in Three Acts with Suggestions for a Project 'The Women of China' for World Fellowship" by Jean Grigsby Paxton, TWP, 1922 (Box 639, Folder 11)
      - "Carrot Skit," n.d. (Box 639, Folder 12)
      - "Cat Fear: A Fanciful Japanese Comedy Pantomime" by Marion Norris Gleason with music by Harold Gleason, TWP, 1916? (Box 639, Folder 13)
      - "A Ceremony of American Democracy" by Rosamond Kimball, 1918 (Box 639, Folder 14)
      - "The Challenge: a 15-minute radio script for use in Centennial program," 1954 (Box 639, Folder 15)
      - "The Child Labor Amendment: An Assembly Program" by Margaret Hiller, TWP, 1934 (Box 639, Folder 16)
      - "A Circus" by Helen Durham, TWP, 1924 (Box 639, Folder 17)
      - "Committee on Space: A World Fellowship Skit with a Sense of Humus" by Barbara Abel, 1959 (Box 639, Folder 18)
      - "The Conspiracy of Spring" by Mary S. Edgar, TWP, 1920 (Box 639, Folder 19)
      - "Consumer Beware! A Dramatization of the Congressional Hearings on Food, Drug and Cosmetic Legislation" by Charline Shelton, TWP, 1936 (Box 639, Folder 20)
      - "The Counsel: A Ceremony for Today in Speech and Song" by Hazel MacKaye, TWP, 1919 (Box 639, Folder 21)
      - "The Crowning of Spring" by Sara Kingsbury, TWP, 1924 (Box 639, Folder 22)
      - "Cryptomeria Tree: A Japanese Play" by Mary S. Edgar, TWP, Program Series no. IX, 1924 (Box 639, Folder 23)
      - "Darkness and Dawn: A Mystery Play for Easter Even" by Frederica Lefevre Bellamy, TWP, 5th printing 1944 (Box 639, Folder 24)
      - "The Deuce of Reducing: A Disarming Skit" by Barbara Abel, TWP, 1930 (Box 639, Folder 25)
      - District School on the Rapidan: or 'Studyin' War no More'" by Harriet C (Mrs. George B.) Ford, TWP, 1931 with "Voices (Box 639, Folder 26)
      - "The Drama of Esther" written and given by the class in religious pedagogy at the National Training School, Mar 1917, TWP, 1919 (Box 639, Folder 27)
      - "The Dress That Came Back" a play for Y-Teen Roll Call Week by Mabel Alice Tuggle, 1950 (Box 639, Folder 28)
      - "Dust and Thrust (A Puppet Panorama in Two Scenes)," Columbus, Ohio, YWCA, 1968 (Box 639, Folder 29)
      - "Dutch Wind and King Grisly Beard: Two Pantomimes" by Madeline A. Chaffee, TWP, 1929 (Box 639, Folder 30)
      - "Early American: A Playlet of the Gifts of the Old Days to the Modern Girl, Indian and White" by Dorothy Cate, TWP 1931 (Box 639, Folder 31)
      - "The Enchanted Urn: A Fantasy in Pantomime" by Hazel MacKaye, TWP, 1924 (Box 639, Folder 32)
      - English-Class Plays for New Americans by Emily M. Gibson, TWP, 1927 (Box 639, Folder 33)
      - "Everygirl" by Mary S. Edgar, TWP, 1929 (Box 639, Folder 34)
      - "Fashion Review: Down Petticoat Lane" by Helen Durham, TWP, 1921, 1926 (Box 640, Folder 1)
      - "The Festival of Days" by Lucy South Proudfoot, TWP,1927 (Box 640, Folder 2)
      - "The Festival of Proserpina" by Margaret Lynch Conger, TWP, 1924 (Box 640, Folder 3)
      - "The Festival of the Harvest Moon, Particularly Appropriate for the Thanksgiving Season" by Sue Ann Wilson, TWP, 1925 (Box 640, Folder 4)
      - "Finance Behind the Footlights: A Finance Campaign in Five Dramatic Flavors" by Barbara Abel, TWP, 1930 (Box 640, Folder 5)
      - "Folk in Our Neighborhood" written originally for the Industrial Department of the Atlanta, Georgia, Association by Martha Jarrell, TWP program series, n.d. (Box 640, Folder 6)
      - "The Forbidden City at Last: A Play of Modern China" by Jean Grigsby Paxton, TWP, 1931 (Box 640, Folder 7)
      - "The Foreign Association Pageant," 1912 (Box 640, Folder 8)
      - "Forward Through the Ages: A Processional of Women" pageant presented at the National Convention, 1926 (Box 640, Folder 9)
      - "Friendly-Kingdom: A Pageant-Play for Girl Reserves" by Tracy Mygatt, 1921 (Box 640, Folder 10)
      - "A Frieze for the Convention Façade" by Elizabeth Russell Hendee, 1932 (Box 640, Folder 11)
      - "From Dollars to Doughnuts" a skit for the National Convention, 1961 (Box 640, Folder 12)
      - "From Morn to Night or A Day at the Y" written and given by the Huntington, West Virginia, YWCA, TWP, 1937 (Box 640, Folder 13)
      - "From Sea to Shining Sea: A Pageant of Brotherhood for Use in Conferences and Similar Gatherings" by Mary Elizabeth Clark, TWP, 1923 (Box 640, Folder 14)
      - "The Gate of Montsalvat" by Mary McKittrick, TWP, 1928 (Box 640, Folder 15)
      - "Girls of Yesterday and Today: Historical Pictures of Association Life," 1915 (Box 640, Folder 16)
      - "A Girls' World: A Radio Script for Girl Reserve Clubs" by Pauline Gibson, TWP,1939 (Box 640, Folder 17)
      - "A Gleam in the World's Eye: a One-Act Kit" by Barbara Abel, 1965 (Box 640, Folder 18)
      - "The Glory of the Task: A Pageant of Woman's Growing Heritage" by Laura Scherer Copenhaver and Eleanor Copenhaver, TWP, 1927 (Box 640, Folder 19)
      - "Go With Us: A one-act playlet" by Henriette Sharon Aument, 1966 (Box 640, Folder 20)
      - "The Golden Leaves: An Operetta of Polish Folk Songs and Dances" by A. Lewis Colwell, TWP, 1927 (Box 640, Folder 21)
      - "The Golden Trail: The Pageant of the 1923 Summer Conferences YWCA" by Jean Grigsby Paxton, TWP, Program Series no. V, 1923 (Box 640, Folder 22)
      - "The Great Standards Mystery: A Play" by Barbara Abel, TWP, 1937 (Box 640, Folder 23)
      - "The Growth of a Nation" by Florence M. Eldridge, TWP, 1926 (Box 640, Folder 24)
      - "Gym and Jerry: A Health Skit" by Barbara Abel, TWP, 1924 (Box 640, Folder 25)
      - "The Health City and Other Plays" by Marion Shepard, M.D.. TWP, 1928 (Box 640, Folder 26)
      - "Here, There, and Everywhere" by Clarette L. Sehon, TWP program series 14, 1926 (Box 640, Folder 27)
      - "Here We Are! A Play in Six Scenes and Three Prospects" by Barbara Abel, TWP, 1930 (Box 640, Folder 28)
      - "Heritage Tea," 75th anniversary, Fort Wayne, Indiana, YWCA, 1969 (Box 640, Folder 29)
      - "The Home Valley: A Pageant for the Little Towns in the Open Country" by Faith Van Valkenburgh Vilas, 1921 (Box 640, Folder 30)
      - "How He Won Her and Four Other Finance Features for Student Association Publicity," TWP program series no. XV, 1924 (Box 640, Folder 31)
      - "How Not to Get Publicity and How to Alienate Editors," skit for training workshop by Elizabeth McCants Drinnon, 1967 (Box 640, Folder 32)
      - "In 1864" by Vida R. Sutton, TWP, 1924 (Box 640, Folder 33)
      - "In Safety: An Incident of the War of American Independence Dramatized in One Act for Pastoral or Indoor Performance" by Margaret Macnamara, TWP, 1924 (Box 640, Folder 34)
      - "In the Forest of Domremy" by Vida R. Sutton, TWP, 1924 (Box 640, Folder 35)
      - "An Indian Swimming Pageant" by Eunice Knox, TWP, 1933 (Box 640, Folder 36)
      - "Intolerance or Bilbo's Tribe" by Mary Hanson, 1947 (Box 640, Folder 37)
      - "Jack-I'-The-Green: An Outdoor Play for a May Festival" and "The Potentate of Weatherdom: a May Day Play" by Margaret C. Getchell, TWP, [1920] (Box 641, Folder 1)
      - "Il Jacobi," TWP 1923 (Box 641, Folder 2)
      - "The Jongleur's Story: A History and Demonstration of Religious Drama" by Frederica LeF. Bellamy, TWP, 1926 (Box 641, Folder 3)
      - "Kay's Idea" by Lillie Johnson Epps, TWP, 1937 (Box 641, Folder 4)
      - "The King of Sherwood" by Ivy Bolton, TWP, 1924 (Box 641, Folder 5)
      - "The Kingdom: A Presentation of the Easter Story" by Karin Sundelof-Asbrand, TWP, 1929 (Box 641, Folder 6)
      - "The Kingdom of Isles: A Water Play for Out-of-Door Production" by Ruth Pursell and Margaret Strassler, TWP, 1931 (Box 641, Folder 7)
      - Lad and Other Story Plays for Children to Read or to Act by Bertha Palmer Lane, TWP, 1926 (Box 641, Folder 8)
      - "Ladies in Transit" a skit by Barbara Abel and Marion Robinson, 1951 (Box 641, Folder 9)
      - "The Lady Joanna and Two Other Plays" by Anne Charlotte Darlington, TWP, 1928 (Box 641, Folder 10)
      - "The Land of Right Side Out: A Children's Festival" by Josephine Thorp, TWP, 1919 (Box 641, Folder 11)
      - "The Legend of the Laurel" by Evelyn B. Brownell, TWP, 1924 (Box 641, Folder 12)
      - "The Legend of Old Manhattan: A Harvest Play for Young People" by Georgia Stenger, TWP, 1927 (Box 641, Folder 13)
      - "The Light of the Women: A ceremonial for the use of colored groups" by Frances Gunner, TWP program series no. 43, 1921 (Box 641, Folder 14)
      - "Lights Up: A Playlet" by Barbara Abel, TWP, War Service Program Series, 1942 (Box 641, Folder 15)
      - "Lights Up For Total Defense," Leadership Division, 1942 (Box 641, Folder 16)
      - "Little Girl, What Now?" a skit prepared by Marilyn Steinbrecher for the Business and Professional Girls' League, 1952 (Box 641, Folder 17)
      - "The Little Patriot" and "Barbara Frietchie" by Margaret Getchell Parsons, TWP, 1927 (Box 641, Folder 18)
      - Little Robin Stay-Behind and Other Plays in Verse for Children by Katherine Lee Bates, TWP, 1924 (Box 641, Folder 19)
      - "The Magic Carpet: A Program on the Near East" by Helen L. Willcox, TWP, 1920 (Box 641, Folder 20)
      - "The Magic of the Deed: a Pageant for the Girl Reserves" by Hazel MacKaye, 1920 (Box 641, Folder 21)
      - "Maid in America" by Marguerite Creamer Pearson, reprint from The Womans Press Magazine, Jun 1937 (Box 641, Folder 22)
      - "Maiden Over the Wall" by Bertram Bloch, TWP, 1919 (Box 642, Folder 1)
      - "Marenka: An Operetta with Dances, in Three Acts" by Era Betzner, TWP, 1924 and "Music for Marenka," 1924 (Box 642, Folder 2)
      - "A Masque of the Seventeenth Century" arranged and directed by Vida R. Sutton, TWP, 1927 (Box 642, Folder 3)
      - "Me For You: A Musical Comedy with Fashion Review" by Helen Durham, revised 1930 by Ethel Gesner Rockwell, TWP, 1930 (Box 642, Folder 4)
      - "Meeting at Four: A Skit for Y-Teen Clubs" by Barbara Abel, TWP, 1948 (Box 642, Folder 5)
      - "A Midsummer Day's Frolic: An Outdoor Play for Girls" by Dorothy Powell, TWP, 1923 (Box 642, Folder 6)
      - "The Ministering of the Gift: Pageant produced for the Fourth Biennial Convention" by Helen Thoburn, 1913 (Box 642, Folder 7)
      - "The Minute Girls Face the Future" by Barbara Abel, National Board Dinner, May 1948, 1966 (Box 642, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous meditations, etc., 1968-71 (Box 642, Folder 9)
      - "Miss Unibrain, 1957" by Barbara Abel (Box 642, Folder 10)
      - "Moments of Courage: 1866-1966" banquet program by Mrs. Rex S. Clements for the National Conference in the Eastern Region, Apr 1966 (Box 642, Folder 11)
      - "Mother Earth and her Children" by Barbara Abel, TWP, 1931 (Box 642, Folder 12)
      - "Mother Nature's Carnival: An Operetta in One or Two Acts for May Day or Any Other Time" by Mildred Olive Honors, TWP, 1928 (Box 642, Folder 13)
      - "Mrs. Tomkins Goes to Market and Other World Fellowship Material" by Katherine H. Barbour, TWP, Program Series, 1936 (Box 642, Folder 14)
      - "The Mystic Flower: An Operetta in Three Acts" by Era Betzner, TWP, 1928 (Box 642, Folder 15)
      - "Neighbors-Not-So-Far" two playlets, two pantomimes, and a story, TWP program series no. VII, 1923 (Box 642, Folder 16)
      - "The New Creation: A Festival," Eleventh National Convention, 1930 and Twelfth National Convention, 1932 (Box 642, Folder 17)
      - "Night and Morning: An Easter Miracle Play" by Margaret Lynch Conger, TWP, 1924 (Box 642, Folder 18)
      - "Now Is the Time: A Choric Drama on the Responsibilities of Christian Women in a War-embittered World" by Lucy Schulte, TWP, Program Papers for Today and Tomorrow, 1941 (Box 642, Folder 19)
      - "The Old Turkish Ring: Three Short Acts and a Prologue" by Cora Clary, TWP, 1931 (Box 642, Folder 20)
      - "On the Line: A Play in Two Acts" by Muriel Ward, TWP, 1930 (Box 642, Folder 21)
      - "One Common Faith" by Lucy Schulte, 1950 (Box 642, Folder 22)
      - "One God" by Lucy Schulte, The Woman's Press, May 1945 (Box 642, Folder 23)
      - One Night Stand. Five One-Act Plays for Young People by Margaret Parsons, TWP, 1942 (Box 642, Folder 24)
      - "The Open Highway" by Ethel Reed Jasspon and Beatrice Becker, TWP, 1927 (Box 642, Folder 25)
      - "Our Heritage" opening meditation for Officers' Training Seminar by Mrs. D.N. Boone, 1969 (Box 642, Folder 26)
      - "Our YWCA International Garden," West Virginia state Y-Teen Conference, Nov 1966 (Box 642, Folder 27)
      - "Out of the Dark: a Pageant of the Negro" by Dorothy C. Guinn, TWP, 1924 (Box 643, Folder 1)
      - "A Pageant of Loyalty" by Dorothy Powell, TWP, 1923 (Box 643, Folder 2)
      - "A Pageant of the Church" by Eleanor B. Forman and Mabel Eleanor Stone, 1917 (Box 643, Folder 3)
      - "A Pageant of the Fifteenth Century" by Vida R. Sutton, Kate V. Thompson, and Adele L. Baldwin, TWP, 1924 (Box 643, Folder 4)
      - "A Pageant of Women in the Sixteenth Century" by Vida R. Sutton, TWP, 1927 (Box 643, Folder 5)
      - "The Palm Branch: An Easter Pantomime with Reading and Music" by Martha Race, TWP, 1932 (Box 643, Folder 6)
      - "The Past is Prelude," 1962 (Box 643, Folder 7)
      - "Pat's Society Circus" revised by Ethel G. Rockwell from the original "Circus" by Helen Durham, TWP, 1930 (Box 643, Folder 8)
      - "The Payoff Cometh: A Postscript to the National Board Agenda" by Barbara Abel, Dec 1946 (Box 643, Folder 9)
      - "Personal Experiences: a Two-Act Play" [re the difficulties and discouragements of stenographers who sought employment during the past five years] by Ada Louise Barrett, n.d. [Depression-era] (Box 643, Folder 10)
      - "The Peterkin Family" by Mary Frances Day, TWP program series no. X, 1923 (Box 643, Folder 11)
      - "The Pledge of the Blue Triangle: A Dramatic Ceremony of Song," TWP, 1919 (Box 643, Folder 12)
      - "Portrait of Lucinda: A One Act Skit" by Barbara Abel, n.d. (Box 643, Folder 13)
      - "Precious Flower and the Flies: A Dramatization of the Story in 'The Honorable Crimson Tree' by Anita B. Ferris" by Helen L. Willcox, TWP, 1920 (Box 643, Folder 14)
      - "The Prodigal Son" and "The Beginning of the Church" by Ava Beatrice Knowles, TWP, 1924 (Box 643, Folder 15)
      - "The Purple Iris: A Story from Old Japan" told by Antoinette Withington, TWP, 1929 (Box 643, Folder 16)
      - "Pygmalion and Galatea: A dramatic sketch showing the appeal of the YWCA to every girl as given by the Class of 1914 of the National Training School," TWP program series no. I, n.d. (Box 643, Folder 17)
      - "The Rainbow Fountain: A Pool Pageant" and "The Harp of Apollo: A Greek Pastoral Fete" for Physical Education Activities by Delphine Harris Coy, TWP, 1930 (Box 643, Folder 18)
      - "Rainy Day Plays" by Margaret C. Getchell, TWP, 1920 (Box 643, Folder 19)
      - "Rameses Dreams: an Egyptian Pantomime" by Marion Norris Gleason with music by Harold Gleason, TWP, 1919 (Box 643, Folder 20)